<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="47">
	<author>LS-Modcompany / kevink98</author>
	
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    
	<title>
        <en>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Fieldcalculator</en>
        <de>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Feldrechner</de>
        <es>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Calculadora De Campos</es>
        <fr>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Calculatrice De Champ</fr>
        <it>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Calcolatore Di Campo</it>
    </title>
    
	<description>
        <en><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Fieldcalculator

You want to know how much seed or fertilizer you need for a field? You can read it here!
You can find the overview in the GlobalCompany menu. To see the seed consumption, click on the corresponding line. Then you can open another window.

Information: Mod only playable in combination with GlobalCompany!]]></en>		
		<de><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Feldrechner

Du möchtest wissen, wie viel Saatgut oder Dünger für ein Feld brauchst? Hier kannst du es nachlesen!
Die Übersicht findest du im GlobalCompany-Menü. Um den Saatgutverbrauch zu sehen, klicke auf die entsprechende Zeile. Dann kannst du ein weiteres Fenster öffnen.

Information: Mod nur in Verbindung mit GlobalCompany spielbar!]]></de>		
 <es><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Calculadora de campos

¿Quieres saber cuánta semilla o fertilizante necesitas para un campo? ¡Puedes leerlo aquí!
Puede encontrar el resumen en el menú GlobalCompany. Para ver el consumo de semillas, haga clic en la línea correspondiente. A continuación, puede abrir otra ventana.

Información: Mod sólo jugable en combinación con GlobalCompany!]]></es>	
 <fr><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Calculatrice de champ

Vous voulez savoir combien de semences ou d’engrais vous avez besoin pour un champ? Vous pouvez le lire ici!
Vous pouvez trouver la vue d’ensemble dans le menu GlobalCompany. Pour voir la consommation de semences, cliquez sur la ligne correspondante. Ensuite, vous pouvez ouvrir une autre fenêtre.

Informations: Mod uniquement jouable en combinaison avec GlobalCompany!]]></fr>	
 <it><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Calcolatore di campo

Vuoi sapere quanto seme o fertilizzante ti serve per un campo? Puoi leggerlo qui!
È possibile trovare la panoramica nel menu GlobalCompany. Per visualizzare il consumo di seme, fare clic sulla riga corrispondente. Quindi è possibile aprire un'altra finestra.

Informazioni: Mod solo giocabile in combinazione con GlobalCompany]]></it>		
    </description>
    
	<iconFilename>store_fieldcalculator.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <globalCompany minimumVersion="1.5.0.0">
        <customClasses>
            <customClass name="GC_AddOnFieldCalculator"/>
        </customClasses>
    </globalCompany>
		
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/GC_Checker.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/GC_AddOnFieldCalculator.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>